Emily DeCrescenzi

South Pasadena, CA 91030 emilyd32_iue@indeedemail.com 323.304.7038

Experienced flora and fauna enthusiast with an extreme love of life. Over three years experience in nursery work with formal horticultural training as well as hands on experience. Lifelong pet parent with experience ranging from small animal rescue to treating equine ailments.

Work Experience

Department Head - Greenhouse

Office experience in both retail and medical environments.

Armstrong Garden Center - Pasadena, CA October 2016 to Present

In charge of ordering all houseplants including many tropicals, orchids and tillandsias.

Maintaining all houseplants to keep them looking their absolute best. Wide knowledge of common and botanical names. Educate customers on general and specific plant care as well as advising them on what plants will work in their environments for optimal success.

Responsible for all other duties in the retail environment such as cashiering, placing and completing special orders and training new hires in all areas required.

Event Server and Lead

Huntington Catering Company - Pasadena, CA August 2013 to Present

Effectively communicate with client, coordinator, chefs and lead in order to maximize efficiency in set-up and service before and during the event as well as post event break-down and cleaning. Other responsibilities include co-leading on large events, working as barista and plating food.

Bookkeeper, General Office Assistant

ICE Sportswear - Pasadena, CA July 2013 to August 2014

Improved efficiency with bi-weekly bookkeeping, executed packaging and shipping and maintained company website i.e. updating product images, pricing etc

Education

AS in Kinesiology

Pasadena City College - Pasadena, CA June 2013

Skills

Skills

- Strong communication skills both in-person and by telephone, proficient in PC and MAC programs such as Word/Pages, Excel/Numbers, etc, both a team player and independent self-starter, efficient at multitasking and coordinating with various team players as well as multiple projects.
- Office Administration
- Google Docs
- Equine Experience